uh another quick video guess what GitHub
thinks directories don't exist let me
show you an error I have it was very
confusing and I was like oh yeah so I'm
going to help you so you do this you do
get I mean wait go test I well you see
my test I ran the test I was like
where's the directory thing this is a
fresh GitHub repo that I just pulled
down that I know worked when I ran go
test before and now that's the test
stopped working you know why because I
had created
the see dur one here the dur one here uh
was in the directory and then it didn't
have anything in it so it didn't keep it
around so all the all the people in my
in my chat are saying oh yeah people
always do they add a dogit keep in there
so the way to fix this is this MK dur
we'll do um uh test data dur one and
then we're going to touch test data uh
dur one dur one/
dog keep and this is a very simple
technique that will make your your stuff
stick around so when I well assuming
something is there why did it not do it
that time I don't know that's a
different problem but this oh I put it
in the wrong place because I'm an
idiot it's supposed to go in Mark what
is it there we
go let's let's try let's do this right
take two um make their
wait what
[Music]
marketers try it again go test there yay
okay it works